What the heck was that all about, Inaba?
Iori's my woman!
Keep your hands off her!
Nothing you need to get worked up about.
I set you up as an obstacle for Fujishima.
Now you just need to do one little thing, and you'll save Iori from the hands of Fujishima.
That's all there is to it.
I don't want to make an enemy out of anyone in the class.
Everyone, except yourself, is an enemy.
What?
Hey, Taichi,
you're in love with Iori, right?
I-I'm in love with Nagase?
How'd we get on this topic anyway?!
Your reactions have been over-the-top lately.
They were a lot duller before all this started.
I'm just being put in situations where I have to react like that!
Just win Iori over before Fujishima beats you to the punch.
I asked how we got on this topic!
And Fujishima's a girl!
Fighting someone to save another.
That's how you like it.
Right?
Selfless freak.
What do you mean by "selfless freak"?
Exactly what I said.
Why'd you volunteer yourself for this waste of time?
If no one wants to do it, then I have to take it on myself.
That way, no one has to suffer through it.
And that makes you a selfless freak.
Why do you like professional wrestling?
It's the art of receiving.
A wrestling match isn't about who can pull off better moves.
A good match is about a wrestler receiving the moves, making the other wrestler look better.
My favorite wrestlers are the ones called "jobbers," who dedicate themselves to getting beaten—
Shut up, you hopeless wrestling fanatic.
But you asked!
Back to Iori.
Don't you get it yet?
She's the weakest link in the CRC.
I've never seen anyone so close to breaking down.
And that weakness is exactly what you want.
You have to be her shield,
get hurt for her, and protect her, right?
It's the perfect job for a selfless freak.
Don't analyze me like that.
I've never thought anything like that.
While we're on the subject, I should tell you that Iori's in love with you too.
Yeah, like that could happen.
What a boring reaction.
She needs someone to set her identity.
Someone who can tell her who she is no matter what.
Plus, you two put on a good show when you're together.
Really?
Well, either way, it's your problem.
You do what you want with it.
But Iori's definitely the most vulnerable.
Vulnerable?
This personality switching can ruin any of us at any time,
but if there's anyone who comes off worse every time, it's her.
"Comes off worse"?
Well, we've only run into some minor trouble so far.
I don't think you need to be so serious—
How stupid are you?!
How can you be so calm about this?
You've convinced me. You are the slowest out of all of us!
This whole affair is a disaster!
We don't know who, where,
or when any of us could get hurt!
Don't you understand that?
Sorry.
No, I went a bit too far.
It's been a long day, and the stress is getting to me.
Sorry.
Will you forgive me?
Of course. It's not like you said anything wrong.
Don't worry.
Okay. Let's get back to picking up the trash.
We won't get anything done if we keep talking.
You really are slow.
Your trash bag got blown away a while ago.
Why didn't you say anything?!
Where'd it go?
Oh, over there!
Because it'd be more interesting if I didn't.
Y-You know,
I always treat you so badly because I don't know how to react.
The truth is...
that I love you, Aoki.
I'm sorry to bring this up all of a sudden,
but I can't keep lying to myself about how I feel!
Will you go out with me?
Did you get that?
I got it.
All right! Your turn!
Y-You know,
I've always...
Um...
I love you!
So, if you don't mind, will you go out with me?
Yes! This is great!
Inaba-chan is always so direct and manly!
But when I see her making such a girly confession... My heart!
And yours is everything you've ever wanted.
Right?
I hope I can get her to say it to me one day.
Well, that's enough for now.
Time to delete.
Wait, wait!
We're not done just yet!
Let's do some more before Yui and Inaba-chan get back!
We might not get another chance like this!
Right?
Right.
Yui, get those phones!
Got it!
It's impossible to move in this body!
Taichi, you need to get more exercise.
Y-You know,
I've always...
Um...
I love you!
So, if you don't mind, will you go out with me?
What an interesting way to pass the time.
Wait, Inaba, what are you doing?
What am I doing? Just getting ready to run around school naked.
P-Please don't, Inaba-chan.
If you do that, I'll die socially!
Then die.
Inaba!
Inaba-san, if I die socially, I don't think I can go on living biologically!
Quiet! You asked for it!
Listen up. If you do it again, you're dead.
Yes, ma'am!
I'm really sorry.
I'm mad at you too.
If you do it again, you're going down.
O-Okay.
Where's Iori?
Did she come in today?
Yeah, but she said that she had something to do, then left.
By the way, I've been meaning to ask...
Yui, are you scared of us two or something?
When I'm in your body...
Whenever a guy comes close, your body starts shaking.
Why would you think that?
Who in their right mind
would ever be...
scared of you?
Um... Yui?
I'm definitely stronger than both of you, you know?
So...
I'm not scared of men!
I'm sorry!
I kept saying that I love you, but I never noticed!
I...
I'm the stupidest idiot on the face of the planet!
Yui!
Don't go after her.
I'll go and calm her down.
Inaba-chan, did you know?
Yeah.
She was really good at hiding it,
so it's normal that you wouldn't notice,
but it's still a big problem for her.
All I can do is lighten the shock.
The rest is up to you.
I'm sick of my own stupidity.
Don't kill yourself over it.
Inaba just said that she was really good at hiding it.
And I didn't even notice when I was in Kiriyama's body.
But there were plenty of hints along the way.
In the CRC, Inaba-chan always hits us because she's angry, or rather, just violent.
And Iori-chan's all about being touchy-feely.
We should've noticed it was weird that Yui wouldn't join in,
considering she's so lively.
You're pretty sharp, Aoki.
We're talking about the girl I love here.
You haven't changed a bit,
even with this personality switching and all the other chaos.
My philosophy is that everything's fine as long as we're having fun.
I think that's all that's important,
and that'll never change.
So I just hope we can look back on this personality switching one day and laugh.
But that might not be possible anymore.
I hurt Yui pretty badly.
What am I getting so serious about?
That's not me at all!
I get the feeling you're more amazing than you look.
Aren't I?
You know, I'm starting to think you'd do better with Yui.
You said that I was amazing,
but in terms of potential, you're way above me.
Potential for what?
You're a natural at it, so you haven't realized it,
but you're amazing.
I don't even know what I need to do next.
Yeah.
How can we save Kiriyama?
That's it!
That's what's so amazing about you!
You jump right to saving her!
That's thinking big!
Well, it's not like I'm thinking anything big.
What scares me is that you might just do it.
But if that happens...
Yui might fall for you!
What?!
I'll call Yui and apologize later!
Taichi! You haven't won yet!
Really?
Okay. If that's what you want, Mom.
Did you like this duo?
Not really.
There's a special on wrestling tonight, so...
After this show's over, okay?
Okay...
Kiriyama?
Um...
I was kind of crying,
but don't let it bother you.
Actually, could you forget about it?
Kiriyama...
can we meet up right now?
Sorry.
I panicked a bit, so your sister might think something's up.
Everyone's been getting suspicious of us lately.
But right now...
Aoki called me right before we switched.
He apologized like crazy.
Over and over.
I was thinking that the both of you might not know how to approach me anymore...
And that we might not be able to have as much fun as before.
I started hating myself for it.
Kiriyama, are you afraid of men?
Yeah.
Is there a reason why?
If so, would you mind telling me?
You always jump right to the point, don't you, Taichi?
You'll be the second person to hear my story, after Inaba.
When I was in middle school, a man attempted to rape me.
Luckily, it was nothing more than an attempt.
I fought back and got away.
But that was back when I practiced karate all day long.
I'd never lost to a boy before.
I thought I'd send them home crying if anything happened to me.
But when it actually happened,
it took all I had just to get away.
Did you know?
Men are really, really strong.
After that, I thought,
"I'll never win against a man."
Hey, Kiriyama.
What do you want to do about it?
I don't really want to tell you.
I want to help you.
That's exactly why.
If I tell you,
it's the same as saying, "Save me."
What's wrong with that?
I'd be causing you trouble because I'm too weak.
For me...
it's more trouble if you stay afraid of men.
I don't want to be like this either!
But...
Then let me help you!
You don't like it either!
You just said so!
I'll show you that you can't lose to any man.
The way you're looking at me is kind of scary...
Don't worry. Just leave it to me.
Grab my shoulder.
Even just watching is pretty painful.
You...
But you get it, right?
You can take down any guy in one—
I'm back!
Serves you right.
That was the most painful thing I've ever felt!
I thought I was going to die!
Taichi, someone's coming.
Should we find somewhere to hide?
It might mean trouble if someone saw us.
Never mind me. Just go.
I can't...
go on...
This isn't the time for cool movie lines!
No... I'm serious...
Excuse me, you two...
Oh no!
Come on, hurry up!
Kiriyama, I think this is far enough.
Oh, right.
No way.
When did I...
You didn't give it a second thought.
That's because we had to get away.
And it's you...
More importantly, what the heck was that?!
I'm a girl! Why do I have to feel a man's pain?!
But it worked, right?
Well, sure, but...
Is it the same for every man?
Yeah.
Don't worry, it's not just me.
I see.
You really can't do anything after something like that.
One clean hit and I've won!
I'll practice more at home.
Have I unleashed a weapon of mass destruction upon the world?
Hey.
Why did you go that far for me?
You even hurt your own body.
Is "I wanted to" good enough for you?
That's so you.
Thanks, Taichi.
Yaegashi-kun,
were you with a girl at the park on 5th Street last night?
Wh-What do you mean?
I thought I saw you all over a small, long-haired girl there.
I take my dog on walks through there.
You've got the wrong guy.
Well, whatever.
I might be wrong, after all.
If so, sorry for suspecting you.
And here I thought I caught you cheating.
Morning, Taichi!
Kiriyama...
C-Could you stop that?
You know, Taichi...
I think I'm starting to get interested in things like martial arts and wrestling again.
Maybe we can talk about them.
Of course! Anytime!
Even right now would be perfectly—
Not right now! Not right now!
Maybe later.
Well, see you.
Go get 'em, Kiriyama.
What do you think that meant?
I knew it!
Something happened between you yesterday!
What did you do?!
I-I didn't really do anything.
I just kind of listened to what she had to say.
Well, not like it matters to me.
But it matters to me!
How can you get close like that just by listening?!
Iori-chan, we need a battle plan!
I said that it doesn't matter to me!
So?
I really didn't do anything.
I just gave her a little push.
I guess good things can come from this personality switching too.
All I could see was disaster...
Inaba?
Inaba?!
Inaba, what's wrong?
Inaba?
Hey, Inaba?!
Inaba?!
Do you want to know, Taichi?
About my past.
You have to take care of your own body.
I thought he might have done something.
Am I your enemy?
And more than anything, actually feeling moved by it is stupid.